It's all good.
>> The Junkyard Love podcast. Okay. So,
let's start with the basics. We were
just talking about awakening. This is a
tough one. Feel free to bring it where
it goes. What is awakening?
>> Well, I think we've not been told uh the
right
uh I don't want to say that we've been
told a lie, but we've not been told
really the the exact um way in which
there's a process to awakening. We tend
to in the western uh to edit out process
for product. Process is more feminine.
Product is more male. So because of the
fact that we have this patriarchal
uh political religious mindset in the
west, we're people of product. We want
things to just happen. But really, when
you go into the great teachers, uh, even
Josua or Jesus, whatever you call him,
he said, "I'm the way." And I think they
cut out the way. You know, there's that
18 years missing in the Bible that
nobody wants to talk about in
Christendom.
>> Like, okay, that wasn't important. He
didn't say anything for 18 years that
maybe you need to know. Uh but I think
that 18 years represents process in the
way that's kind of been cut out of
Christianity as we know it today. So I
think that uh there's a process that's
that's missing in the fact I think we're
being told that somehow awakening is a
an event rather than an unfolding and
that we can just wake up in paradise and
bliss and all that's kind of the new age
uh idea. Now, I've been very part of new
thought, new age, metaphysical for
decades, but I'm finding myself at a
place where I'm re-evaluating a lot of
that teaching. Not that I don't believe
it didn't serve, but I think there's a
shift, a paradigm shift that's going on.
And I think we all need to stop and take
a pause and kind of look back at some of
the things that we've all taught and
influenced people with that actually has
not brought forth the fruit of what we
have said. And that's where I am after
decades of research and doing what I'm
doing is like okay what of what I've
taught what what am I seeing that is
basically kind of happened.
>> So I really kind of see this idea of um
awakenment is is a
a process of moving us into seeing first
what we call the illusion of the world.
I don't think that awakening is a bypass
around it. I think it's through it.
And I think that people need to be
empowered as to how do we navigate
through this time of breakdown. I was
asked by my higher self, I guess you can
say. But the words formed in me in the
uh about 20 25 years ago when I started
my business with soul energetics, this
uh vibrational tuning fork work. Um, do
I want to try to fix what's breaking
down or I want to work with what's
breaking through? I didn't even know
what that meant 25 years ago in my
intellect. But something in the cells of
my body said I want to work with
breakthrough. And now I've to realize
that there is there's higher frequency.
I call it 5D just for communication
reasons. But uh the dimensions beyond
our 3D 4D world I think is um breaking
through new information new data new
direction is coming in and of course the
reason I know it's breaking through
because the old is breaking down and so
rather than trying to fix people I've
tried to awaken people to the fact that
the path that they really are on should
be the path to no path. In other words,
I don't think we're in lack trying to
get something we don't have. I think we
need to realize what we have forgotten,
>> you know, and and we've kind of lost
oursel in the what course of miracles
calls the dream, the world of insanity.
It's called many different things. The
the maya, the illusion, uh world of
appearance and all of that. And I think
we have to wake up from that. And to
wake up from that, we have to see it for
what it is first. So waking is not a
immediate experience of I'm in bliss now
and everything is wonderful and great. I
think that actually we find oursel a
little disoriented at this time and
we're in a uh we're in the midst of this
state of of chaos. So I'm awakening up
to a lot of things that I've even taught
and believed that I'm re-evaluating what
I've taught and believed. So, I'm in a
great transition period uh for myself uh
in where I am. And I think a lot of
people are kind of in that place and
don't realize it because and we're not
telling people that's okay.
>> That's okay.
>> Uh this is probably the most spiritual
times to be alive on the planet right
now, but it doesn't look like the best
time. It's kind of like the idea of the
best and the worst happening all at the
same time. you know, the the the idea of
um the best of times and the worst of
times is happening at the same time. Or
there's a scripture that says the great
and terrible day of God. So, I think
we're in the most terrible day, but the
great day spiritually uh that people are
waking up and realizing that
all of this that's going on in the world
politically and not just politically,
but in every system is not new. We just
haven't seen it. We have stuck our head
in the sand. And a lot of us who have
been spiritual, newagy type people has
offered people all this euphoria of
bliss and everything is great and ignore
it. And I think we stuck our head in the
sand, so to speak. And I think people
are beginning to realize, no, I'm here
to look at it for what it is, but see it
from a higher state of consciousness and
start raising the vibration of
consciousness. So, we need to be working
in the in the collective level. Anyway,
I could go on and on about this, but I'm
I guess I'm just sharing with you an
experience that I'm going through at
this time of my own awakening that's
taking place.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Uh as it's an active
awakening, it's not it's not as it's
only something you you had an awakening
experience and now you're this, you
know, just this person, now this diff
this different person. It's an active
thing. Uh Ken Wilbur talks about I'm
sure you've looked into Ken Wilbur in
integral theory but he talks about this
maturation maturation process and I feel
like when I was first listening to him
talk about it um it it was so simple and
so profound. It was a little bit like
kind of one of those remembering things
that you you're talking about. It's
like, oh yeah, I I kind of know this,
but it seems so obvious when he when he
points it out basically, you know, we go
through puberty in the physical body uh
when we become a certain age and and
that's an obvious thing. And it's, you
know, it's not necessarily an arrival,
it's an active through a few years and
we change and we develop into, you know,
not only a societal different version of
oursel, but a you know, our physical
body has transformations, male and
female. Um, but also there's an active
uh like psychological
self version of maturation, puberty
that's going on. Um, and and it's
>> it's almost like it's happening at a
more rapid pace, not only just to more
people, but um we're covering more
ground at once. like you know just
through the internet and just through
knowledge and books and and exchanges
like this. We get to consume so much
amazing information all so very quickly
and it can expand all of our
consciousness at we essentially can
mature faster these days as it seems.
>> Yeah, you're you're saying some really
good things there that I really like.
>> Yeah, feel free to jump in.
>> Yeah, I think that uh uh that things
have intensified with information. We
are in the age of information, no doubt
about it. And I think people can get
overwhelmed with it. You know, there's a
place uh in in the text that says that
knowledge can make one weary. And I
think people sometimes get so bogged
down with all this uh that's on the the
media, on the computer, on YouTube. I
know I can go down that rabbit hole and
I hear one and another one jumps on. I
go, "Oh, that's good." Until I just like
want to shut down to it all. But one
thing that I've tried to teach to people
or to remind people, I'm really not a
teacher. I'm a reminder.
>> Nice.
>> Uh and to remind people that all this
knowledge is coming to you from outside,
whether it's in a book or whether it's
on a podcast or where it's coming from,
it is your responsibility to see what of
that data or knowledge resonates with
your own innate intelligence.
I don't think there's anything that we
need
uh in the sense of what we don't have
and gathered outside of oursel. So when
you take things like what we're doing
today as a podcast or what I do is doing
lectures and and all that I do and that
type of thing, I'm very clear to tell
people don't believe everything I say
just because I say it. Don't follow me
in my teachings because I'm going
through a process. I'm just doing it
publicly and letting you hear it. And uh
I tell everybody to take because you
hear something. Somebody may hear us
today and go, "That was really
interesting. Now I don't know what I
think about it, but that was
interesting." Now, if it was
interesting, it caught your attention.
Therefore, you hold it and contemplate
it in a neutral state. Don't judge it
right or wrong, good or bad, but just
hold it. Now if it is for you, it will
resonate your own innate intelligence
and you'll have your own aha moment or
your own epiphany and that carries your
own I am code or signature to it because
we don't want other people's. We want
self-nowledge and I'm talking about the
nosis self. Not the self we think we are
but the true self that's waking up so
that we have direct knowledge with God.
I don't know if you've been much into
gnosticism, but it has changed so much
for me to study that in in some way. So
anyway, that's kind of the way I want
people to to see it from my point of
view.
>> Yeah. So So innosticism, do you mean uh
like studying the self and what what the
self is and and changing your uh how how
you view yourself?
>> Yeah. Well, you know, nasticism is is
the pre-Christian
uh the first two centuries
before
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Before we took an organized it into
religion uh in Nika when it became a
national institutionalized religion,
there were those that were called the
heretics,
>> which I identify with the heretics.
>> Yeah. more than I did the the uh those
who organized it and and made it into
dogma and doctrine. But if you really
read back at that time, what they were
all seeking was nosis in the Greek,
which is direct knowledge. Not knowledge
through a preacher, a priest or a rabbi
or through a a church or a religion, but
direct knowledge. And of course, that
became at some point a threat to what
was organizing. So they had to shut that
down. And um that's where I think we get
those who were seeking that way begin to
take what they were learning and begin
to write it and put it. And that's what
we found hidden in the caves in 1945
uh was the Nagamandi uh library like the
Gospel of Thomas and all of that that
didn't make it into the Bible. But now
it's showing up because I think they
were wise enough to know, you know what,
they're going to come along. they're
going to suppress this and they're going
to change it. So, let's let's leave a
trail for those for that generation that
will come. And I think that generation
really is the generation of after World
War II around 1945. Then you have a
couple more years later and you have the
Dead Sea Scrolls. So, you're starting to
see a lot of suppressed knowledge and
information uh begin to show up. But
again, it's not to be made into another
religion, but it is to be used as a tool
to resonate our own innate intelligence.
And that's what I love when some when I
speak, the greatest compliment I can get
from somebody who's waiting at the back
of the of wherever I am and they'll say
to me, "Thank you for saying that. I was
trying to I was already getting that,
but I didn't know how to say it.
>> That tells me that what you got came
from you, not me. I was just able to
help you to uh to bring it into your
consciousness on an individual level.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's it's certainly a
remembering. Um it reminds me of Ramdas.
He would talk about how he just has
these you know hypnotic audiences and
they're just listening falling for 45
minutes and then he would almost kind of
break the barrier and go how how why are
you guys all nodding? You know how do
you know this stuff? You know
>> it is that's how it is. You know it is a
remembering. It's it's a it's almost a
clearing the small self out of the way
so that the the bigger self, the bigger
you, the bigger God, whatever is is
shining through instead, you know.
>> Yes. Yes. That that's that's what I'm
trying to
>> that's the relationship I try to have
with an audience of any kind.
>> And you know, even Buddhist said, don't
believe anything the first time you hear
it. And I think we have to be careful
about what we qualify as information
into a belief system.
And one of the things that I've taught
through my energy work and through my
vibrational sound work is that whatever
you qualify into your belief system is
the blueprint that cells read as they
replicate themselves.
>> Yeah. So people's got to change the
blueprint. It's not just changing the
knowledge, but it's what you've
qualified into your into your etheric
blueprint that is going to make the
difference. Yeah. Yeah. So that reminds
me, it just sparks uh you know Bruce
Lipton in the epigenetics uh
conversation. So um I I would love to
explore a little bit of that. How do you
understand epigenetics and like how
certain genes express versus not
expressing?
>> Oh, that's my subject. Yeah, this all
started with me in the 80s around ' 86
and 87. Uh I was uh in a deep uh silent
meditation time in which I was really uh
opening myself up to receive some
direction where I was to go and I heard
formed in me the words deox deoxyraic
acid. Well, and I still don't know how
to say it. It just shows you it wasn't
into my intellectual at all, but I knew
it was DNA. And uh uh I won't go into
the whole story, but but uh the story is
that after I heard that, I didn't know
what to do with it. And it was kind of
at the time that we were uh cracking the
code for the genetic uh genome.
>> And I remember President Clinton at that
time getting on say that we're very
close now to having the genome
completely completed. And I thought, hm,
that's interesting. They're starting
about DNA. And then when we went through
the u the trial of I can't think of his
name, the the football player and OJ
>> and constantly we heard about uh uh DNA
uh act DNA work was going on. Anyway,
the words DNA was just everywhere and I
thought, oo, this is entering the
collective consciousness somehow.
>> So I just said, well, I don't know
anything about it. I'm not a geneticist.
I'm not a scientist, so that probably
has nothing to do with me. Well, it
wasn't a couple of weeks that I got this
call from somebody I had heard of in
years and said, "David, I was told to
call you and tell you that there is a
teacher out here in California that's
teaching DNA activation workshops."
>> What do you mean they were told? Did
they have they had like a they heard
something too?
>> Yeah, they were like an intuition. Yeah,
they just had this I came up to them
after all these years and uh it was Dr.
Robert Gerard who was doing this. Well,
I I I thought what you can change DNA. I
thought that was set in stone.
>> Yeah.
>> But I got on the internet and they were
having a an intensive workshop in
Scottsdale, Arizona. And I called a
friend out there thinking I'd stay with
you and I went out there and took this
intensive workshop uh about DNA. And so
we learned a a lot about DNA in several
days. It was an intense thing. And then
we were given these um at that time CDs
that had these sounds that had been done
by people who has observed people doing
energy work from Reiki to whatever and
DNA. And so we were uh we were taught to
go around and do DNA activations using
these sounds in the background. Well,
that's what started it with me. So, at
that time, I was u exposed to
six different frequencies that had been
taken out by the church in the 17th
century called sesio.
Uh which were sung in the chants of the
church, but they were so powerful that
they took them out. Um, and they took
out like the word the first one was oot
quint laxes in Latin and they changed it
with do and do became a deer
>> and you have Julie Andrews you know with
that kind of thing. So these frequencies
had been brought back. Well, one of them
was 528 hertz. Now you may have heard of
that one because it's pretty popular and
it's the heart love frequency of the
sofasio frequencies. And so I was going
around doing these little DNA activation
workshops that I had learned and I
thought, man, I got to have that 528
hertz uh because I read that the jennas
were using it to repair DNA. And I
thought, I got to have that. Well, 528
to the brain, which generalizes would
sound like a C uh above a C on the
piano, but that's not 528. It sounds
like it, but it's not 528. it's a
different frequency. So I thought, well,
that won't work. Uh cuz something was
telling me you'd have to have exact
frequency. You can't have a generalized
frequency. So that's when I learned
about the Sopesio 528. And I thought,
well, there's no instrument that plays
it. We have nothing in the west at all
because western music is called 12 tone
temperament, which is C to C, which is a
closed octave. Closed octave. So most of
our music boxes us in uh rather and
that's why we tend to go to Eastern
music for meditation or whatever because
it's not boxed in music, right?
>> So anyway, I got another call from
somebody I had heard of in a long time
and in the conversation they said to me,
"Did you know that you could have any
frequency made into a tuning fork that
you want?" A tuning fork? All I knew
about a tuning fork is my folks had a
piano and they had a little guy come out
with a tuning fork and every year and
and would, you know, change it. Um, but
anyway, at that time I learned that that
528 was a part of five other Sopio
frequencies and some things that just
order them all. And I'm telling you, it
changed my life when I got those forks.
I didn't know what to do with them. But
anyway, the 528 was about DNA. And um
when I got into the atheric idea, I
thought, "Wait a minute. We have
ancestral DNA, but we also must have an
atheric DNA above it." Well, I didn't
know above in Latin means epi
>> above. EPI is above.
>> Wow.
>> And then when I I was so ready for Bruce
Lipton, it was like, "Oh my god, thank
you." Because everything he was saying
was coming alive in me. And I thought
I'm tapping into epigenetics.
>> So you know uh our ancestral affects us
about 50%. But the other 50% is our
choices, our our attitudes, our
thoughts, our food we eat. And that's
epigenetics that we have this ability uh
to take responsibility of that type of
thing. So anyway, I ended up getting
downloads in how to teach uh etheric DNA
work with tuning forks and I was blessed
in Stanford uh uh university to find a
bio
genetic guy who was ready to give me the
frequencies of all all the DNA letters
uh of the AC gt alphabet of the DNA. So
for 25 years I've taught DNA activation
uh work. I still do it. I've taught
people how to I can go back and say that
there is six generations back that is
affecting some of the things you don't
understand about yourself because it's
not yours. It's it's theirs.
>> So we go back and rewind those
generations back into that. Now I've
sold that company. I don't have it
anymore but I still do the my you know
my own work. But I I sold it a few years
ago to another couple that's carrying it
on. But it's still me, you know,
teaching all this stuff in S Energetics.
>> So then I ended up here in Charlotte
with as a leader of a spiritual
community called Heartlight Spiritual
Community as their spiritual leader. And
now I've started this academy in which
is all my teachings that I've been doing
all along. Now you mentioned something
while ago that I really really want to
uh visit and that is the fact of
adolescence and all that. I've been
teaching for years that there are three
stages of our spirituality. Babes,
adolescence, co-creative adults.
>> Okay.
>> And I really got that from my Bible
background. You know, I've spent years
of the Bible.
>> Mhm.
>> I wasn't a good fundamentalist at all. I
was a rowdy one. I was always shaking up
these, but I remember it talks about and
the babes in Christ shall give the
sincere milk of the word. And then it
says, I when I became an adult, I put
away my childish things. And then it
says, until we grow uh into the fullness
of the stature, being no more children,
being tossed to and fro by wind of
doctor, but growing up in love. I
thought that's the thing that's been
missing is Christianity have never
taught us growth. It's just get saved,
wait for Jesus, go to heaven, blah blah
blah blah. And again, they've taken out
the process. So, I said I'm going to
step in and be the process guy.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Wow. Okay, dude. Oh, wow.
What What a great way to uh to to like
zoom in on that. I really like that. I
think that's brilliant. Yeah. They they
don't seem to teach growth. But what
Okay, I I've thought this for some time
and I've heard other people say it on um
on podcasts and stuff and and it really
makes me contemplate. Do you think that
um there used to be some form of uh
tradition or coming of age? Like there's
a lot of speculation that um back in the
day these people would do psychedelics.
They would have some sort of ceremony
and they would you know you by doing
psychedelics you lose connection with
your old self and you you know you have
a new identity shift inevitably. Um, and
so like maybe there's a large portion of
the Bible or what we call Christianity
that's missing this whole section of
maybe this ceremony, this religious
tradition, this uh we drink this urgot
or we take this psychedelic and we have
some sort of journey, some sort of
experience that brings us coming of age
as a man or something. Um, do do you
think anything like that could be could
be true or have you stumbled upon things
like that in your research?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, in in
in my religion I was raised in which was
extremely fundamental
Pentecostal,
>> right?
>> I mean, really, I never fell for it, but
I was raised in it. My my own aunt was
my pastor.
>> My uncle was the overseer of the of the
denomination, so I was right in the
middle of it. I was in it, but I wasn't
of it.
>> But anyway, and our we taught is 12
years old is the age of accountability.
And I think they got that probably the
fact that Jesus was around 12 years old
when he was in the square astounding the
physicians.
But this is the craziest doctrine
because it meant that the minute I turn
12, I need to get saved or I'm going to
hell. Up to 12, I'm covered.
Now, that's what they believed.
>> That'll scare you.
>> Yeah. So that was that was the ceremony
they went through is come down give your
life to Jesus get saved at 12 years old.
That's the ceremony. Now if you go back
into more Catholicism and and those kind
of churches they they baptize the baby
immediately because the baby can go to
hell if it's not baptized. So
everybody's got some kind of a
traditional way into the kingdom uh of
God on earth that's different. And of
course, indigenous people had their own
ways, but it seems like it's innately in
us to have this moment of crossing over
from being a soul to being a soul in the
human body and the human story. So, it's
it's something that doesn't seem to be
learned, but I think it's innately in
people to do that. But again, I'm not
sure it's the outer age or all of that.
I think it's stages of consciousness
that we're really dealing with here that
people are missing. And I think people's
been in Christianity for years and have
have never left the babe stage. They're
still babies.
>> And I think there's people that got
stuck in adolescence.
And I think there's very few that have
grown up to take co-creative
responsibility to realize that the
creator is not going to do everything
for me, but I'm going to work with
creator to create a new heaven, a new
earth, a a new
realm, a dimension on this earth. And
that's what I think people are beginning
to awaken to is new responsibility of
entering into the process of destiny.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I mean it really is
this constant uh you know in in in Zen
or or in Buddhism they talk about the
beginner's mind. You know, you have to
have those life experiences that bring
you into the beginner's mind and that's
really what what the awakening is. You
know the the fancy flashy awakening that
we hear about of like the initial like
whoa I have this sudden kind of
realization which isn't the full story
of the awakening as we've already
discussed but that is kind of like the
the the recognition that pulls us out
into recognizing that we need to go on a
different path. we need to start
listening to this different intuition.
We need to make changes in our life.
That that sort of thing. Um so you've
probably come across a lot of people um
in my notes I had written down uh kind
of some different terminology of
awakening. So I wrote I I think you had
you use the term cellular awakening and
then I also just kind of wanted to bring
in both spiritual awakening and
condundalini awakening. So are these
would you treat these as different
things or are these all kind of like the
same thing happening we just use
different language for?
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah. Very good. Uh when I say cellular
awakening,
uh what I believe is um for for decades
we have been very uh attached to the
within message.
Go within meditation. Go within.
Everything has been within within.
Within I think in the 80s Shirley Mlan
made it uh a big
impression on people who began to
meditate.
uh TM kind of made a revival from the
'60s and people began to really rise.
It's within. It's within. And you still
hear the within. But I think that which
was within is beginning to find
frequencies and vibrations to not stay
within but begin to come out.
>> In other words, I have had wonderful
experiences by going deeply into myself.
Now you can do that through meditation.
You can do that through certain drugs uh
or whatever you know uh that are
available out there and there's many
ways that you can have these wonderful
experiences within yourself but that's
not helping the world
>> right so what I think is people are
beginning to have the experience of
what's within them start coming out and
when they do it enters the cellular
level
and therefore
Uh I I've seen people
I've seen people I know in my group
they're right now they're having a real
issue because we're starting to see a
demonstration at the cellular level. In
other words, we're not so about quiet
all the time, but it's like people want
to do something with their hands or
their arms or even there's a certain
dance that is coming forth and people
are moving and they're saying, "What's
happening to me? This is not me." You
know, I thought serving God was a quiet
inner thing and all of a sudden they're
feeling all this where they live in the
in the cells of their body. And I'm
saying because this is the coming of
Christ.
See, I've heard Christ is in me. Christ
is in me. The divine is in me. The
divine is in me. But when it comes to
where you live, it starts changing all
the frequencies, all the patterns of
your humanity begin to change
themselves. And that's the change that
we're in. And unfortunately, not
unfortunately, but fortunately, when
that happens, we don't understand what's
going and we get misdiagnosed. We think
something's wrong with us. We run to the
doctor and the doctor says sometimes,
"You're fine, but but I'm not sleeping
at night. Uh or my eating habits have
changed or I don't know where these
added moods are coming from." But what's
happening is what's inside both not so
good and good is coming out
right and people are experiencing it
right where they live. And there's a
place in in where it says that Jesus
said which maybe he did in the book of
Thomas he said when the inner becomes
the outer and the outer becomes the
inner up becomes down becomes up male
becomes female and so on so forth then
you shall behold my kingdom upon the
earth. So we got to we got I keep
teaching people let this come out. Don't
keep going in and visiting visiting it.
But what you've been visiting and
enjoying inside of yourself wants to
manifest itself. And the church has
called that the coming of the Lord, the
coming of Jesus, the coming of Christ.
But it's what's coming is inside of
ourselves. And our cells are changing
their frequency and their vibrations.
The spin of the electron is changing.
The molecules are changing. And when
when the molecules start changing uh and
science has quantum science has proven
that if you watch a certain atom like a
hydrogen atom and it it's going to
change into a lithium atom that the
first thing that it does is become
unstable at the molecular level
>> and it goes into chaos
uh but and disorder. But what disordered
it was order
>> because it can't become the next thing
until it has lost the old pattern. And
then they observed through the telescope
that out of that um chaos one molecule
comes over here and leaves all of that
and becomes still and then two. Now when
two molecules come together they create
something greater than the sum of the
parts and they activate the law of
attraction. So two becomes four, four
becomes 16 and critical mass is reached
and when critical mass is reached then
it jumps to the next level of its
evolution to become the next thing. Now
if that happens at the molecular level
what's happened at the human level? The
same thing. So transformation begins
with chaos. And I want people to
understand that this is not something's
wrong. How did I fail? I thought I
thought serving God was going to be a
wonderful experience. It's exactly what
it's supposed to be. And you're here for
that. And you've been equipped for that
to go through that.
>> So okay. So what is it about the human
experience? What is it about like you
know us with this ego thing that can you
know a caterpillar you you've spoke
about caterpillar becoming a butterfly
before it becomes absolute mush in the
in the cocoon. It just becomes complete
mush and you know as we are in the
process of becoming complete mush and
becoming a butterfly of our version. Why
is it that we hold on so tightly? Why do
we like does a does a caterpillar into a
butterfly have this? No, I don't want to
become mush. I'm refusing it. I want to
stay the same. You know why? Why do we
have that?
>> Uh well, it's it's it's something in our
evolution.
The thing about evolution that has
served us to this point is our ability
to adapt and survive, which we have
done. We have survived about five or six
extinctions on this planet. We're in the
sixth one right now. And we have gone
through wars and famine and racism and
slavery and and and genocides and all
that and we've made it through that.
Now, here's the thing. There's a line. I
don't know where I got it, but I really
like it. But it says, "What blesses you
in the beginning can betray you in the
end." So what's happened is we become so
accustomed to adapting
uh to things as they are
that when something tries to change it's
not familiar to us
and we begin to resist it and even
though we say I don't like where I am I
want to be somewhere else when that
starts happening we tend to go back to
what's familiar to us and that's what I
think is kind of the push and pull that
is going on with with people right now.
Now, I always make the statement that
old caterpillar doesn't go through what
it went through to be an enlightened
caterpillar.
>> Yeah.
>> And what we're going through is not to
remain an enlightened homo sapien, which
is an adolescent human, but we are to
become the next level of our evolution.
And therefore it takes that breaking
down
to happen. And I think that this is
right on. I think people are asking who
am I?
>> Uh where am I going with it? And these
are very spiritual questions I think for
people to explore uh with themselves and
to find out what what is going on. So I
love the caterpillar thing. Um there
there is one place in the Bible I really
do like a lot and it says we shall not
all sleep but we shall be changed in a
moment in the twinkling of an eye. And
that word change in the Greek is
metamorphu.
>> So it's not talking about like changing
something. It's talking about a complete
transition and transformation into
something completely different like the
caterpillar becomes the butterfly. And
the word moment there doesn't mean in a
moment, but it is the Greek word auto
atomos which we get the word atom from.
So it says we're going to be transformed
all the way to the atoms of our body.
>> This thing about the Bible, you got to
break it down. It's not English. One of
the first awakening points I had when I
started ministry at 17 years old was
nobody in the Bible spoke English.
I thought, where did that come from? Cuz
I thought the Bible, God spoke English,
Jesus spoke English, and I thought, none
of them spoke English. So, what did they
say? So, I started looking into Greek,
Aramaic, and Hebrew, and finally
Sanskrit. And I said, this is not what
they said at all, what the Bible says.
So, I started talking about that, and
people started listening to me. and I
kind of developed a little following of
people who wanted to know
and and whatever. So that was an
awakening point for for me. Well, of
course that awakening point was a bliss
because I thought I had it all figured
out in my belief system. I thought
because the Bible said this, I believed
that. And then when I looked it up in
the context of the language and the
culture, it didn't say that at all. So I
had to change my whole belief system all
over again. Yeah.
>> And so I've done that many times, by the
way.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I always find it
interesting when I have kind of new, you
know, I I elevate my wisdom or my way of
looking at the same thing that I used to
look at in a different way. It's always
like, man, how did I how did I believe
that for so long? Or and then you kind
of observe other people, you're like,
"Wow, you have a whole you have you
react in your life to,
you know, an incorrect belief system, so
to say." like I I you kind of wonder how
did you get that out of reading that you
you know uh it's very and then I also
kind of I I don't really understand how
people could just trust like all right I
read it and it's been translated through
all these different languages and
through these different people and
through word of mouth for a lot of it
and then they just read it like it's
just word for word every single word
that's translated to English is
>> is like God's word and so I yeah I don't
know I I don't get how you it's very
exciting for need to read those and want
to explore that more like okay what did
that mean in that time like you said
what did that mean in that language in
in their um
>> you know in in their history so yeah
okay so I I would love to kind of zoom
zoom a little bit back if you will David
um I I would like to go so we've
mentioned a few times already that you
spent a lot of your years as um in in
ministry so I would love to kind of jump
back and ask you kind of about your
young years um in spirituality and and
kind of what your experience was like
young and then maybe leading up to your
kind of awakening into changing.
>> Very good. Sure. Um I consider myself
someone who um I could really get into
some things. I'm going to try to hit the
right points.
I like to say I had a different rapport
with time and space from the very
beginning. And it was something I didn't
learn because what I was learning in my
tribal first chakra family was not at
all what was happening inside of me. But
at a very young age, I knew that I had
somehow a different direction of life
than what I was being shown at that
time.
I questioned everything.
Why did I do that? I asked my higher
self, whoever want to listen and they
said to me because there is a critical
mass of souls who have been born
consciously
and I thought what does that mean? Well,
this got pretty deep into there. But
what it said is there is a certain
amount of souls who have incarnated
through a different portal than the
portal that most people incarnate into
3D world.
And oh my gosh, this took me back to the
beginning with the Elohims. You know,
when it says in the beginning, God,
there's no word God there in the real
translation. That's from the Greek.
That's from the German word for good.
That we got this word God. Goot was too
gruttle for us. So we said God, but now
it's really the Elohims, which is God's
little G, male and female as a group. So
this group came down out of the sky and
and uh begin to mess with DNA and all
kinds of I'm not going to get all that,
but but it gets there's a whole story
there if you look deep enough in into
the Bible. And I keep tell don't throw
the Bible away because it's coded. We
haven't even understood it yet. Why do
you want to throw it away when it's so
coated deeply? Uh but you got to get
past all the many translations and man's
insertion of his doctrines and doctr
dogmas to get to it. Uh whatever. But
when these Elohims came, they were the
true representatives of creator, let's
say. But as creator changed its
frequencies and got more dense and more
dense and got to earth as
representatives of itself collectively.
Um
um when it hit the earth
the thing about the earth it's a free
will planet.
That's why it's some of the hottest real
estate that's in the galaxy in the
universe is the earth because it's free
will. And when they got here, they chose
to not represent the true creator but to
become the creator. So they usurped the
creator to become it. And but not all of
them. Part of them says we are not going
to follow the darker Elohim. And
therefore they were banished from the
earth into the star systems
>> like pallades and so on and so which is
in the Bible. Pades and all that Orion
is in the Bible. And we know that 80% of
what makes up our atoms is star stuff.
Anybody can look that up and check that
out. But you're made of star. We're star
seed people. So they were banned off of
the planet until 2,000 years ago. One of
the light Elohims made it into the
planet called Yeshua or Jesus and
created a new way and portal for us to
incarnate and not be dumbed down by the
technology that was being used on the
earth to dumb down people so they didn't
get it while they were still in the
physical body. I know this gets crazy.
>> Very interesting. Yeah.
>> But but it's the story that unfold. It's
there for anybody if you want to dig
into it and look into it. So I believe
that a lot of us have incarnated
uh without being dumbed down that we
come in with some memory.
This isn't right. This world as it is is
not my home. Uh I don't fit here.
Right? And I'll guarantee the people out
there that's listening to us that are
part of that are feeling that. They may
not understand it, but they're going,
"That's me. I've always been the weird
one in the family. I never followed what
my siblings followed or my my parents."
That's a good thing because it shows you
that you're here with purpose to be here
on the planet. All we have to do is just
remember who we are and reach that
critical mass. You know, the hundth
monkey story kind of thing. So, when we
reach that, we will we will call this
cause this shift to take place. But I do
believe that when Jesus said, "I'm the
way."
He's saying, "My teachings is the way,
not me. Don't serve and worship me, the
man."
He didn't come here for that. He came
here with a message that hadn't been
dumbed down. And that message is the
message of Nosis. And and and the church
is so busy worshiping him that they
really don't get into his teachings. and
they took out that 18 years of his
teachings. That is part of our process
of getting back to where we can remember
why am I here? What is my purpose to be
here?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. I I always
wonder the 18 years that you
>> Yeah. Hey. No, I I love it. I I I it's
ve very wonderful, very interesting. I
feel like there's a million other things
that I could ask. Okay. So you you
certainly were, you know, born awake,
born conscious, as you say, right? Is
that what you say? Born conscious.
>> Born conscious.
>> So at what point did you start, you
know, cuz I'm sure there was a good
amount of, at least through your young
years, that the the teachings that your
family and the the um the the Jesus
things that you were learning around you
probably did make sense. What was kind
of the changing point for you where they
started to like the teachings in that
book just weren't matching?
>> I love that question. Thank you.
>> First of all, when I was 5 years old, I
would go visit my grandma on the farm.
>> Okay.
>> And I found myself preaching to the
cows.
>> Nice.
>> And I would preach to Bessie and I'd
say, "Bessie, get that lipstick off or
you're going to hell."
Now, that's what I'd heard in church.
See, that's all I knew. And Bessie would
look at me and go, "Mo, like,
I'm not a sinner.
Don't be putting me in hell." And it it
planted something in my mind. Maybe
we're not the sinners they said we are.
Maybe we learn to be the sinners that
they are. But what actually happened to
me was around 17 years old. And I was uh
drawn to
an event that was happening in Tulsa,
Oklahoma. It was a literally a movement
that happened. It was an 8-week revival
that was going on down the street from
my church and I would pass there. I
thought, "What is going on in this
place?" I mean, there was cars
everywhere every night. And uh so I went
and snuck into this place. Now, I did
not want to be known because I was known
as my aunt's nephew. I was their piano
player. So, I kind of got in the back.
And this preacher was preaching 90 miles
an hour and carrying on and whatever.
And there was maybe 800 people in there.
It was huge. And all of a sudden, he
just stopped,
walked down the aisle, and looked right
at me and says, "God just said to me, he
sent you here today. Do you want what
God has for you?" And I'm going around,
"Who is he talking to?" And I realized
it was me.
And I said, "Well, yes, sure." He said,
"Well, come up here." and I started down
the aisle and I never made it to him.
Something came over me and knocked me on
the floor.
It was like 220 hit a 110 body. Couldn't
handle it. And I laid on the floor on
that floor. And I won't go into all of
it. Some of this is in my books, but I
laid there and got three visions
that changed my life. Now, I went down a
skinny, introverted kid
dealing with a lot of issues
of my difference.
But when I got up,
this voice bmed out of me and people
started listening to me and asking me to
come to their church and to all these
things. And I began a ministry at 17
years old. Wow.
I pastored my first church when I was 19
in Montgomery, Alabama during the race
riots of that time. And that was what 64
years ago that I started that and I've
never stopped. And I've continued to
grow. I've continued to challenge a lot
of traditional religion with love
because I know where people are. I know
where they need to be and they need to
be there until they're not. So, I'm not
out to convert people to anything, but I
think there are those that are a level
to hear this message that uh I and
others are really bringing right now uh
to do that. But that's how it started.
And to this day, I can just open my
mouth and get up and I don't organize
sermons. I don't prepare. I don't
rehearse. I just get up and spirit just
speaks through me. I just constantly
channel
>> what I call my higher self. And it's
been a very good successful thing that I
do. Now on the academy for instance, we
have Bible 101 classes. So I try to meet
people where they are and teach them
what does it mean sin? What does hell
mean? First book I ever wrote was hell
yes or hell no.
So I've tried to meet people there. And
then I've got other things for people
that are more adolescent. they're out of
that, but they're not quite into the
more mature teachings and they're kind
of in between there. So, we're trying to
meet everybody along my path that I've
made that might be kind of looking to
find support, you know, on the path that
they're on in that in that way like
that. But yes, 64 years ago, I started
being a full-time minister and I need to
write a book. I've had a lot of
experiences. I've never joined a
religion. I've never joined an
organization. I've never been a part of
a denomination. I have totally just
walked and trusted uh God, universe,
whatever you want to call it. And it has
been with me right to this point that I
am today.
>> Wow, that's so fascinating. Yeah, I I
didn't I didn't realize that story. I
didn't know about that. That is so cool
to hear. U what what an incredible, you
know, invitation into the into the life
that you've lived. I mean, really kind
of a an initiation into into purpose.
That that was one of my questions for
you was uh kind of like what is purpose
and and like how are you living through
purpose and and I feel like like you've
already answered that question. You know
>> I don't mean to interrupt you but it's
living me. I'm not living it.
>> Living through you like live
>> it's living through me.
>> Yeah.
>> Absolutely. Absolutely. Um okay. So I'm
really fascinated curious. Have you
heard of the there's a spiritual teacher
um he's pretty popular on YouTube but he
he's an author. He's written a book. His
name is Aaron Abkey. Have you heard of
his name?
>> I don't recognize that name, Ronald.
>> So, he was a he was a a pastor's kid
from a young age. Um and he was teaching
ministries from a very young age. And
then um he started having some questions
and then started reading some more
eastern uh eastern psych psychology. Um
started exploring different theology
outside of just like his one religion.
And he had kind of these awakening
experiences. And now I find that he
bridges um I feel for me he's helped me
bridge a lot of the western and eastern
ways of understanding things like oh
yeah they're talking about the same
thing and this is just another brilliant
way to put it and all that sort of
stuff. Um
>> and it's and on top of that I'm really
drawn to you know Alan Watts did a great
great work of
>> bridging those two gaps and and that
sort of stuff. Um, so I guess I I I kind
of am curious where you see that that
bridge happening. Um, not only in like
your own teachings, but just kind of in
the in the modern times like this this
connection between Western and Eastern
like are we going to pop out on the
other side with just an understanding of
kind of the whole thing or you know
where do you see that going?
>> Okay, you just asked the right
questions. Thank you.
>> Good. Uh,
a scripture that comes to mind, in fact,
it's one of my slogans that I use at the
center is, "Who shall stand in the gap
and make up the hedge?"
Now, we're living in a world that's
dying, but a world that has not fully
stabilized itself. The 3D systems are
all like the caterpillar going to mush.
It really is. I don't care if it's
financial, educational, political,
religious, medical, everything is like
the caterpillar going to mush and and
going into state of of disorder.
But the new systems that are trying to
come in, which the Bible calls the
kingdoms of this world, you know,
kingdom should be systems of this world,
uh has not really stabilized itself. So,
we're living between two worlds.
That means we've got to have those who
are instructing us, empowering us, and
directing us, who are in between, and
who will stand in the gap. And the names
that you were mentioning are those, and
I'm trying to do the same thing. That's
why I still use the Christian language.
I still will throw in scripture while
I'm talking Buddhism. I will talk a
cabala, but I'll use scripture because I
try to bring everybody back to where
they've been at the same time where
they're going, but where they are right
now in this gap between the worlds. So,
I really admire those who have not
totally cut the past out because a lot
of people need to be reached who are in
that level. So, um, that's that's my
intent is to be able to use the language
of 3D with a 5D vibration or frequency
to it.
>> Yeah. Nice. Okay. Um, so I do want to go
back towards So, I want to go back
towards tuning forks and frequency and
um, those sorts of things. So, a little
bit of my background just to fill you
in. I've been a paid DJ for 14 years. I
do a bit of a musician myself. Um, so I
have I'm an audio engineer. Um, so I, so
I I I have my levels of understanding
with with music and frequencies and, uh,
you know, uh, we have this thing, um, in
one of the programs I use, it's called
the Camelot wheel and, um, it's
essentially like a different wheel of
keys and it's, you know, it's
color-wise, it's the same hue, uh, like
you know, your hue color selector and
any old thing, it's the same sort of
thing and it correlates, you know, the
different keys hit this different color,
which correlates to the different
motion, those sorts of
Um, and I bridge the gap with, you know,
our chakra systems, you know, our
different color chakra systems,
simplified. Not always like, you know,
you play the red one, it always
activates root chakra feeling in you.
But there is some some truth in that.
And I've I've witnessed it on dance
floors and I've I've built hourlong
journeys and those sorts of things. And
and you know, I I've brought people in
dancing and ecstatic dances to places 45
minutes in that like they just couldn't
have gotten there without this this
bridge, so to say, I guess, from
starting from the very beginning, you
know? And when I'm building those sets,
you know, I'll be at home when I'm just
trying to gather ideas and and get
samples and songs. And I feel very very
intuitive when I'm building those sets.
It's almost like I'm projecting myself
into that room, like what do these
people need? who's going to be in this
room, what's going to work through them.
It's it's really fun. I mean, it's such
a
>> Wow. I love it. I love it.
>> It's It's such a fascinating experience.
Um, so I I think I I kind of wonder
>> to to throw that back towards you. Um, I
I kind of wonder I don't know if you see
yourself as like a an artist or a
musician much, but um I kind of see you
as that way. I wonder like with your
tuning forks, do you have an intuitive
kind of like thing that comes through
for you that's like building something
for other people that's kind of um using
these sound and these frequencies as
ways of like like he like I guess do you
see yourself as a bit of a shaman in
some sort of ways at all when you when
you use your tuning forks?
>> I'll take that.
>> Sure. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Call me what you will.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Well, that's that's an interesting qu
thing. I think I'd like to start with
the fact that u uh when I was a young
man, I mentioned my aunt was my pastor
>> and she had this wonderful kind of
bluesy jazzy voice.
>> Oh, nice.
>> And she would take me over to the
African-American church on Saturday
night when they would do these radio
broadcasts and she would sing. And when
I would listen to the singing,
I thought, what is different?
The way they sing Amazing Grace and we
sing it as white people.
>> Yeah.
>> They were using more black notes, more
more dissonant type notes. And it just
resonated with me. And I sat there and I
thought, I want to know this. So, uh, I
hired a little girl from Paradise
Baptist to come and teach me. Now, I was
playing piano for my aunt by ear. I've
had no lessons. But one one Sunday, my
aunt, who was up preaching and had lost
her piano player, spun around on her
sixinch heels and pointed to me, I was
10 years old, said, "David, you're going
to be my piano player." And my dad had
taught me C, F, and G. That's all I
knew. And I went to the piano. I loved
her so much. She started singing When
the Saints Go Marching In and my fingers
started flying.
So I learned to play that kind of
gospel. But the the the black gospel
thing really caught my ear. And I
learned to play enough of it that that
very church hired me as their organist
>> for for $25 a week, which in 1962 wasn't
too bad. And by the way, this church was
in Tulsa in Greenwood. If you know the
Greenwood massacre story,
>> I'm I'm unfamiliar.
>> Yeah. 1901 was one of the worst
massacres of Black Wall Street was in
Tulsa. It's hardly talked about, but
it's now coming out what went on. And
there I was in the middle of all of
that.
>> So, I became very interested uh in that
kind of music. To make a long story
short, I ended up traveling with Mahalia
Jackson, who was the you're you're
young, but she was the gospel
queen of uh gospel music uh back in
those days. And so I ended up more in
that culture of music and liked it. I
still am. I still do it. Uh I still
sometimes it just comes out in me and I
do those those kind of uh uh things like
that. So I have no training in music
whatsoever but I play by ear and I just
can do what I do. Either that I don't do
what I do but as I said earlier the
thing about western music is called 12
tone temperament. Are you familiar with
that?
>> Um a little bit a little bit.
>> All right. If you go all the C to C
white black note you go 12. So a full
octave is 12 and then you box it in. You
close it.
>> Well, what's happened now that's so
fascinating is we've gone back to
Pythagoras
who said and and looked up into the
heavens and the skies and said, "How do
I get to heaven to earth?" Speaking of
the stars and whatever and came to this
genius idea, let's not close the octave.
So when he didn't close the octave, he
found the spiral
of the of the atmosphere of of
everything. And we know now that NASA
has found out there that's not empty
space, but it is sound coming off of
moons and planets and whatever that
everything is connected by vibration and
sound out there. So he brought heaven to
earth in the music of the spheres. it's
called. Anybody can look it up and find
find his work. Um, so he's a great
player in a lot of this new idea of
using more dissonant sounds than just
linear A B C D CDE E FG. But he began to
put in these unusual sounds that was
bringing in higher sounds of of planets
and and whatever. Well, that fascinated
me and I I connected that to the
sofasio. Have you heard of sesio?
>> I've heard of sesio. Yes.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, the sofasio to me are
bridge
between Pythagoreans's um comma.
Pythagoreans comma is the space of the
overshoot of the octave in which there's
a little bit of space there. And it's in
that space that we find the spiral
because the universe is a vortex and
spiral. That's why we are attracted to
chakras chakras
because they spiral and they connect us
to the bigger spirals of the universe
itself. They are many universes in us
that we can deal with. I mean the
chakras are are taking too much u you
got to really realize the power of
chakras are amazing. It's it's it's an
amazing thing. So anyway um
unfortunately western music like
everything uh came along Rockefeller and
them and all them they changed the 444
to 44A. Uh they did it on purpose. I
hate to say it, but they did it for the
fact of keeping people limited and boxed
in through the music. And that's what
happened to me when I heard the black
gospel music. It wasn't boxed in music.
Now, shooting forward later and getting
into more newagy whatever and I started
meditating. I could not meditate to
western music,
but if I heard something that was
eastern,
I could do it.
And most people do if you think about it
go more in new age go more toward
eastern type sounds more Hindu more
whatever now the idea of the
condundolini
just merely means that we have not used
the supply of energy that we've been
given for a lifetime
because we stay in survival mode and
therefore that energy has been pulled
down through the crown and ends up at
the coxix
>> and that's one thing that I was given to
teach people through tuning forks. I had
three frequencies of tuning forks to
activate the coxix
to connect people's personal energy
field to universal energy field. So it
was like taking their because I I teach
I'm teaching a class right now called
energy is currency.
>> So sometimes we don't have enough beyond
survival to manifest what we want. So I
march people down to the World Bank,
central bank where all the money is and
we withdraw it and then through the
shackles we distributed into the energy
anatomy body
>> and this gives us more abundance of
energy to to work with to create and to
manifest with in that way. So that's
what condundolini is kind of means to
me. I know that's an eastern term, but
actually it is about the energy that is
at the coxix level that we have not
used.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I like your emphasis on it
on it having been stuck in it like when
it comes out. It's the condalini
experience. I I was kind of curious if
you can I was thinking of you know if
anybody's listening or watching that is
kind of unfamiliar with any sort of
energy work or raiki or um you know
maybe even they don't know much about
yoga or any of this sort of stuff. Could
you tell what is it like when you um I
mean you you've now passed it down, but
when you were the person doing these um
these healings and you're actually using
your your your forks and you have them
in your hand and things like that.
What's going on in like person to
person? You know, I've seen videos of of
you know, bodies moving around and
people having, you know, tears coming
down and that sort of thing. Is is it a
bit like that?
>> It can be. Everybody's different.
Everybody responds very differently. But
I'm working totally in the atheric body.
I never touch the physical body.
>> Physical body is totally effect. I'm
working in cause. I'm working in that
blueprint. And that's the thing that's
beautiful about energy work like that
that people just don't get is that we
know now that every disease that's
coming into the physical body is in the
atheric blueprint 9 months to a year
before it gets there. So, I've taught
people how to use the tuning forks and
listen to them and feel where there's
blockages in certain aspects of the
atheric body that's connected to that
chakra. So, let's say it ends up in the
first chakra. Well, that means something
from conception to six or seven years
old has not been balanced somewhere in
that person's unconscious part of them.
So we we intuitively can find that by by
experience and learning. You you know
it's not just going to a workshop and
learning something. You got to practice
it. You got to cultivate it. It becomes
an art to you. And I've taught people
all over the world. Uh we had teachers
all over the world. They're still out
there uh that that teach this this
method. But if it's already in the
physical, then we can find where the
root of it is in the etheric part of the
body that's connected to that chakra. So
then we go in with these combination of
sofasio frequencies and learn how to
create an environment where the person
if they're ready to release it. We don't
make people release things they're not
ready for, but we create the environment
for them to let it go if it's not
serving them any longer. So, I never
disempower anybody by saying, "I'm the
healer. I'm the one out here doing this.
I'm just facilitating
what's inside you that has gotten stuck
and that you're not connected to." And
this is the the wonderful thing about
vibration. I think tuning forks is
perfect
example of pure vibration. It has no
emotion to it. You know, I hear songs
and I have an emotion. I'll think who I
was breaking up with, who I was falling
in love with, where not a tuning fork.
You just hold a tuning fork and it's
just pure raw vibration.
>> And I see them as keys to the kingdom.
When Jesus gave Peter the keys or David
played the keys that drove the evil
things from Saul called the keys of
David, I believe the Sopesia were the
keys and that's why the church took them
out by the 17th century because it was
the key to open us from mankind to
godankind, our own identity as the
divine made individualized
in the human story.
>> Wow. Wow. Okay. Um, what what is Yeah, I
know. I feel like I've sparked with so
many fascinating questions, man.
Amazing. Uh, what are the what are the
tuning forks made out of actually?
What's what is the material?
>> Uh, they're mostly alloy, which is very
important because there's a lot of cheap
ones out there that are tiny and they're
not alloy. But alloy actually came from
another planet. So, it's one of the most
strong wonderful things for pure
vibration that there is in my research
of that. So, it's very important. We had
the best. Uh we paid a little bit more.
We were more expensive than others. And
others have got China's got a bunch of
them now. Now when I started was there's
very few of us that had it, but now
they're everywhere. You can get them
from other countries, but they are so
cheaply tiny. Uh whatever. So you want
the best uh I think which is alloy,
>> right? Yeah. I'm sure at this point if
you hear a cheap one, it probably really
spins out to you.
>> Like Yeah, definitely. Um I well so I
would also love to ask a little bit more
about um the spiritual community that
that you live in. Um just for for a for
a quick intro on that. My my curiosity
comes from um I've been a meditator for
probably eight years now and I've had an
opportunity to go to a good handful of
meditation retreats and I just I just
love them. I mean they're just who
doesn't love meditation retreat, right?
But um just being around so many people
where you can have spiritual discussions
and you're kind of away from the hustle
and bustle and you know typically when
I'd go on a retreat it's you know I've
I'm on some sort of vacation from work
so I've set aside that time so it has
that to it of course too but um
>> I I would love to just kind of like
learn more about your your spiritual
community and kind of like what what
life is like for you guys there.
>> Yeah. Uh Heartlight Spiritual Center uh
if anybody's interested to check it out
it's heartlightsharlotte.org.
or
um we have a beautiful place. Uh I took
it over eight years ago. I was brought
in as a speaker and the minister said,
"You just got to come here and be a part
of this. We want you." And so I moved
from Columbus, Ohio to Charlotte and it
did not work well working together. It
was just didn't work out. So she bowed
out and I ended up with it. And so I
redid the whole place and redid
everything and started over again and
made it Heartlight Spiritual Center. Uh
it's it's uh we have Sunday morning
services at 11:00. It's a very diverse
group of people. Uh everything is
diverse, the music is diverse, the
teachings are diverse, and a lot goes on
there. That's that's wonderful. I do a
Wednesday morning class every Wednesday.
Uh we do chiong and uh we do that. We
also just built an oasis with a
heart-shaped labyrinth tent uh
meditation gardens and whatever. And so
there's just a lot of my teachings on
there. If anybody's interested in
heartlightsharlotte.org, you can get all
my all my videos and things like that
there. But I'm really trying to direct
people to the uh spiritual awakening
academy for spiritual awakening because
that's where the teachings are that I'm
trying to leave as my legacy. Uh I just
turned 80 years old and uh great for
>> Thank you. And for 64 years I'm like
thinking, you know, things in the next
year or two may may change and I want to
settle down and probably just do work
online. Uh, I want to get my own
podcast. By the way, how you like this
name of podcast? From sin to Zen.
>> Oh, I like it. I like that. That's good.
I think. Yeah.
>> Yeah. From Zin to Zen. So, uh, that's
kind of my plan. And so, I want to leave
this legacy of all my major teachings
that I have on the academy. And there's
a lot on there that's free that people
can get if they want to check check it
out. Okay.
>> Uh, that'd be great. And we'll give you
all that information. So, you'll
>> Yeah,
>> you'll have that if you'd like. Anybody
uh anybody listening right now or
watching know that those links are down
below. I've included those in the bio so
they can just click on those.
>> Wonderful. Thank you so much for that. I
appreciate it.
>> Yeah, of course. Um okay. Well, so
here's a here here's a strange question
for you.
>> What do you have to So if someone is
interested in your academy, what what
would be kind of your your elevator
pitch on it? Like say they they didn't
know much about you and they hadn't just
listened to this whole conversation
between us. what what what is it and
what do you have to sell, you know?
>> Well, first of all, again, it's my
legacy and I think that people who are
on a path I've been I've been there. So,
I think they'll find their where they
are on the academy.
>> So, I want to support them where they
are. Maybe they're not. Uh, you know, I
have some pretty far out stuff on the
academy, but maybe it's somebody that's
just come out of religion and the church
and they're still wrestling with some of
the dogma that's still in them that they
haven't quite figured out. Maybe they
stay I don't believe in hell, but deep
down they're wondering, well, maybe is
there still one? So, I'm trying to give
people the knowledge to understand
because the truth will make them free,
right? And sometimes people say they're
free, but they've come out of religion,
but religion hadn't come out of them. So
before you get into chakras and you get
into this deeper uh it's very stuff I'm
talking about, you might find yourself
there that some people are way down the
line somewhere. So there's something for
them. So, I'm kind of leading my my
footsteps that I've taken that maybe
others might find a way that I can be a
blessing to them because I didn't
sometimes have anybody. Some of the
things I've been a real pioneer. I'm a
true Sagittarian, but I am a pioneer.
I've just gone out there with nobody to
support me, nobody to say, "Yay, you're
right." or whatever. I've just launched
it. And so I think it's important if you
stop and think about uh interstates at
one time they were just pathways and
they were dirt roads and they were but
thank God for those who went before us
and made a way so we can do things
easier. And that's my desire of the
academy that people will find it easier
to grow and to mature and to get some
maybe answers to some of the questions
that they still have that's holding them
back.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Brilliant. Wow. That's so
good. Yeah. It reminds me I I have this
um this line from a poem that's uh like
leader a leader catches cobwebs in his
mouth and says nothing.
>> And then I was also thinking about um
>> like you were saying you're you're a
pioneer. Oftentimes I feel feel myself I
I resonate with that a little bit. Um I
call myself a bulldozer sometimes, you
know, not in a derogatory way, but yeah,
sometimes I do feel like I'm out there
with a machete and I'm just like I don't
really know exactly where I'm headed,
but I I got to trust it and you'll see.
I think I think we'll see, you know. Um,
yeah. So, I think there's people at the
edges that are trying to like guide
people into something that intuitively
feels right for them. And I really I
really like what you said about, you
know, they'll find something on their
path within all this all these years of
work and all this information, this
wealth of knowledge that you have to
offer. Uh, I think it's it's pretty
likely to say there's probably something
in there for anybody who's kind of
poking their head into this.
>> All my books are on there. You can get
my books. You There's just a lot of
things to look at. So, anybody just
interested there there's kind of a a
free uh thing of of of samples that they
can they can just check it out and see
may you know maybe it's for me, maybe I
should know more, maybe not. So,
>> yeah. Yeah. Well, amazing. Uh we are
getting up here in time, David. Um I
will again I'll include all of those
links and everything down below and
everybody will will know where to where
to find you and they can stay in touch
with you if they'd like to. Um, as we
turn the corner and and we um we we come
to turn the page, I I wanted to ask you
if there's anything that feels left
unsaid, is there anything at the tip of
your tongue or anything that you kind of
wanted to mention today that comes up
that you'd like to throw in?
>> Yeah. Well, if we ever do this again,
I'd like to get on contracts and
agreements made previously to your
incarnation
because there's a a great uh activation
going on right now of contracts. we have
forgotten that we have made that's going
to change and transform people's lives.
So that's uh an area that I think people
can understand more what's happening to
me. You know, I'm sure that old
caterpillar goes, "What in the world is
going on here?" You know, I've been
nibbling on this leaf and now there's
I've eaten all my resources. I have
nowhere to go. But what's happening
inside of me? I don't know what's
happening. And I think people don't
understand what's happening to them. And
they're not victims to God. They're not
victims to it. They've already uh
co-architect this change that we're
going through. It's already in them.
We've just forgotten it. But I think
that it is time that some of these
things when I work with individuals uh I
will find out that uh I had somebody
last week and I found out that in
October of 2027 a new contract is going
to be activated in them that they made
that's going to change their entire life
and the trajectory of their world. Get
ready for it because you're in for some
real changes of direction that's getting
ready to happen to you. So, um, that's
kind of what would be on my mind for
another time maybe or something like
that. We could
>> Yeah, I know. I'm I don't want to invite
us into another 30 minutes of contracts,
but now I'm now I'm really interested.
Um, uh, oh, I I I will leave it up to
the listener to explore more on what
contracts sparks with that if they can
find more info in in your work.
>> Um,
>> wow. This has been great. So great
talking.
>> Yeah, likewise. Thank you again so much
for your time, David. Um, this was so
great and and honestly, you know, just
just thank you for your work. Thank you
for your life's work. This is really
cool stuff. This is um, like I said, you
know, I'm really drawn to kind of these
that that in between that that bridge,
you know, um, I love learning about it.
I love um, talking having these
conversations with people about it. And
so um, yeah, just thank thank you for
your work, man. This is awesome.
>> Oh, you're welcome. I I I'm appreciate
what you're doing to give us a platform
to be on here and and uh you're you're a
great a great voice that's out there and
there's so many right now that are
joining and to
>> Yeah.
>> the voice to awaken so many people that
are ready.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I uh as I say probably too
much on this podcast, but as Rome says,
we're all just walking each other home.
>> That's right. I like that. Yeah. Yeah.
So, um All right, man. Well, um let me
let me end this recording. Uh listeners,
love yourself. Drink some water. As I
always say, if you haven't drank any
water today, come on. What are you
doing, man? Stretch a little bit. Yep.
Hydrate. Stretch. Love yourself. And uh
click down below. Check out more of
David's work. David's work. And uh we'll
see you next time.
>> Hello and welcome to the Junkyard Love.
>> Hey, everything's going to be all right.
>> It's all good. It's all good.
>> The Junkyard Love podcast.
Three to the junkyard.
Hello and welcome to the junkyard love.